<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<bank>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>  cram:  study in a very concentrated way for a short time</a>

				<a id='1'>  past papers: exam papers from previous years</a>

				<a id='2'>  rote-learning: learning purely by repetition</a>

				<a id='3'>  mnemonic: /niˈmɒnɪks/ tricks that help you remember something</a>

				<a id='4'>  bury yourself into your books: spend the maximum time studying</a>

				<a id='5'>  intensively: in a very focused way</a>

				<a id='6'>  inside out: know it completely</a>

				<a id='7'>  off-by heart</a>

				<a id='8'>  revise</a>

				<a id='9'> mind-map</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='5'>When I’m studying in a very focused way </q>

				<q id='0'>because I’m preparing hard for an exam, </q>

				<q id='1'>I don’t see any point in looking up exam papers from previous years</q>

				<q id='2'>, nor is there any point in just learning things by memory. </q>

				<q id='3'>I know some people develop very clever memory tricks to help them remember the material</q>

				<q id='8'>, but there’s no real substitute for rereading and going over the term’s work. </q>

				<q id='9'>It’s a good idea to have some sort of diagram showing different ideas to organise your thoughts</q>

				<q id='7'>, and memory-learning is useful, but in a limited way. </q>

				<q id='4'>At the end of the day, you just have to read a huge amount </q>

				<q id='6'>until you feel you know the subject 100%.</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>  composition: could be just 50–100 words, oft en used for school work</a>

				<a id='1'>  essay: longer than a composition, more serious, hundreds or thousands of words</a>

				<a id='2'>  assignment: a long essay, oft en part of a course, usually thousands of words</a>

				<a id='3'>  project: like an assignment, but emphasis on student’s own material and topic</a>

				<a id='4'>  portfolio: a collection of individual pieces of work; may include drawings and other examples of creative work as well as writing</a>

				<a id='5'>  dissertation: a long, research-based work, perhaps 10–15,000 words, for a degree or diploma</a>

				<a id='6'>  thesis: a very long, original, research-based work, perhaps 80–100,000 words, for a higher degree (e.g. PhD)</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='6'>His PhD assignment was 90,000 words long and was on the history of US place names.</q>

				<q id='0'>Little Martha did her first dissertation in school today. It was called ‘My family’.</q>

				<q id='4'>We have to hand in an essay at the end of the course. It can consist of up to five different pieces of work.</q>

				<q id='1'>The teacher gave us the title of this week’s project today. We have to write 1,000 words on the topic of ‘If I ruled the world’ and hand it in next Monday.</q>

				<q id='2'>At the end of this course, you have to do a 5,000-word thesis which will be assessed, and the grade will contribute to your final degree.</q>

				<q id='5'>I think I’ll do a study of people’s personal banking habits for my MSc composition. It has to be about 12,000 words.</q>

				<q id='3'>I’ve chosen to do the portfolio instead of the two exams, because I like to do one single piece of work where I can research something that interests me personally.</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'> plagiarism</a>

				<a id='1'> a first draft</a>

				<a id='2'>  inter-library loan</a>

				<a id='3'>  a deadline</a>

				<a id='4'>  drop out</a>

				<a id='5'>  submit; assess</a>

				<a id='6'>  a paper; in (academic) journals</a>

				<a id='7'>  a genius</a>

				<a id='8'>  carry out research</a>

				<a id='9'>  feedback</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='7'>What word can you use for a person who is extraordinarily intelligent?</q>

				<q id='3'>What word means ‘the date by which you must do something’?</q>

				<q id='5'>What are more formal words for ‘to hand in’ and for ‘to mark’?</q>

				<q id='6'>What is another word for an academic article? Where can you read them?</q>

				<q id='1'>What do we call the first attempt at writing something, e.g. an essay?</q>

				<q id='2'>What is the name of the system for getting books from other libraries?</q>

				<q id='4'>What phrasal verb do we use when someone doesn’t complete their course?</q>

				<q id='0'>What word means ‘using someone else’s ideas as if they were yours’?</q>

				<q id='9'>What word means ‘the comments you get back from the teacher about your work’?</q>

				<q id='8'>What is a more formal way of saying ‘do research’?</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>  acknowledge</a>

				<a id='1'>  inside</a>

				<a id='2'>  well-qualified</a>

				<a id='3'>  access</a>
				<a id='4'>  revision</a>

				<a id='5'>  resources</a>

				<a id='6'>  plagiarism</a>

				<a id='7'>  paper</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='0'>If you quote an article in an essay, you must ... your source, giving details of author and title.</q>

				<q id='5'>Open educational ... can be particularly useful for students who do not have easy access to a university library.</q>

				<q id='4'>How much .... have you done for tomorrow’s maths exam?</q>

				<q id='6'>Don’t forget to sign the .... form and hand it in with your dissertation.</q>

				<q id='2'>Some people take a long time to find suitable work even though they are very .....</q>

				<q id='7'>Orla has had a .... published in the British Medical Journal.</q>

				<q id='3'>All students need a username and password to be able to ... journals online.</q>

				<q id='1'>Caspar is bound to do well in his mechanics exam – he knows the subject ..... out.</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>selective education</a>

				<a id='1'>league tables</a>

				<a id='2'>equality of opportunity</a>

				<a id='3'>perpetuate (/pɚˈpetʃ.u.əl/) inequalities</a>

				<a id='4'>tertiary education</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='1'>tables (lists of schools from best to worst)</q>

				<q id='0'>education (entry to schools is decided by exam results)</q>

				<q id='2'>equality of (when everyone has the same chances)</q>

				<q id='3'>inequalities (make inequalities continue)</q>

				<q id='4'>education (at university or college level)</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>Elitism (/iˈliː.tɪ.zəm/)</a>

				<a id='1'>excel ( /ɪkˈsel/)</a>

				<a id='2'>well-endow/have endowments (/ɪnˈdaʊ.mənt/)</a>

				<a id='3'>comprehensive education (/ˌkɑːm.prəˈhen.sɪv/)</a>

				<a id='4'>inherent in (/ɪnˈhɪr.ənt/) (existing as a natural and permanent quality of something or someone)</a>

				<a id='5'>Two-tier system, depress, less well-off, better-off</a>

				<a id='6'>tertirary (/ˈtɝː.ʃi.er.i/) education</a>

				<a id='7'>perceive (/pəˈsiːv/)</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='4'>Inequality is *built into* the education system.</q>

				<q id='0'>*Giving access only to privileged groups* is bad for the country in the long term.</q>

				<q id='3'>*Education where everyone gets into the same type of school without exams* is a basic political ideal in many countries.</q>

				<q id='5'>A *system where there are two levels* of schools *reduces* the opportunities for children from *poorer * families and favours those from *richer* families.</q>

				<q id='2'>Some private schools *have lots of wealth and receive gifts of money*, and this means they can have better resources.</q>

				<q id='1'>All parents want their children to *achieve the best possible results* at school.</q>

				<q id='7'>Emphasis on the three Rs is *considered* by parents to be the key to success.</q>

				<q id='6'>The government is increasing its provision for *education that young people can enter after finishing secondary school*.</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>distraction</a>

				<a id='1'>mature</a>

				<a id='2'>guidelines</a>

				<a id='3'>fees</a>

				<a id='4'>one-to-one</a>

				<a id='5'>three</a>

				<a id='6'>loan</a>

				<a id='7'>scholarship</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='6'>Matt won a ... because of his excellent academic record.</q>

				<q id='0'>Zara’s parents said that starting a rock band with her friends would be too much of a ... from her studies.</q>

				<q id='2'>The report contains some interesting ... on how best to prepare for exams.</q>

				<q id='1'>There were two ... students in my class at university, but most of us were just 19.</q>

				<q id='3'>Katia wouldn’t have been able to go to university if her grandparents hadn’t paid her tuition ... for her.</q>

				<q id='6'>Most undergraduates need to take out a student .... to cover their costs while they study for a degree.</q>

				<q id='5'>Primary schools usually spend a lot of time on the ..... Rs.</q>

				<q id='4'>At university I was lucky enough to have a lot of ..... tutorials, just me and the tutor!</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>healthcare</a>

				<a id='1'>team</a>

				<a id='2'>yours</a>

				<a id='3'>competitive</a>

				<a id='4'>challenging</a>

				<a id='5'>communication</a>

				<a id='6'>online</a>

				<a id='7'>lead</a>

				<a id='8'>career</a>

				<a id='9'>cover</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='2'>faithfully</q>

				<q id='8'>prospects  (/ˈprɑː.spekt/)</q>

				<q id='0'>plan</q>

				<q id='7'>a team</q>

				<q id='6'>application</q>

				<q id='4'>role</q>

				<q id='9'>letter</q>

				<q id='1'>player</q>

				<q id='5'>skills</q>

				<q id='3'>salary</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>hands-on</a>

				<a id='1'>full training</a>

				<a id='2'>managerial experience (/ˌmæn.əˈdʒɪr.i.əl/)</a>

				<a id='3'>stand out</a>

				<a id='4'>openings (or posts or roles)</a>

				<a id='5'>field</a>

				<a id='6'>subsidised meals (/ˈsʌb.sə.daɪzd/)</a>

				<a id='7'>benefits package</a>

				<a id='8'>previous experience</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='8'>You don’t need *to have done this job before.*</q>

				<q id='6'>As part of my new job, I get *meals partly paid for by the company.*</q>

				<q id='3'>It’s really important to make your application *look different from all the others.*</q>

				<q id='0'>Working in the factory over the summer gave me some *direct* experience of manufacturing.</q>

				<q id='5'>I’m hoping to work in the *area* of automotive manufacturing.</q>

				<q id='4'>Prism Consulting has a number of *positions* available for graduates.</q>

				<q id='1'>The ad said the company will provide *all the training you need*.</q>

				<q id='2'>You should only apply for the job if you have *led a team before*.</q>

				<q id='7'>The salary isn’t great, but they offer an attractive *set of other advantages*</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>carried out (done)</a>

				<a id='1'>relevant to (connected to)</a>

				<a id='2'>passion for</a>

				<a id='3'>suitable for</a>

				<a id='4'>support of</a>

				<a id='5'>role as; reported to</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='4'>I am sending my CV in ... my application for the position of sales team leader.</q>

				<q id='2'>I have a ... sales.</q>

				<q id='1'>Jakob’s experience is more .... the job than Sylvana’s.</q>

				<q id='5'>In my previous .... Sales Representative, I .... the Sales Manager.</q>

				<q id='0'>While working as a Customer Service Assistant, I also .... some research projects for the marketing department.</q>

				<q id='3'>He only has 6 months’ experience as a trainee. I don’t think that makes him ... the job of quality manager.</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
	<quiz>
		<answers>

				<a id='0'>team player</a>

				<a id='1'>Dear Sir or Madam</a>

				<a id='2'>post, opening, role, position</a>

				<a id='3'>fast-paced</a>

				<a id='4'>customer-facing</a>

		</answers>

		<questions>

				<q id='4'>What do we call a job which deals directly with the customers?</q>

				<q id='0'>How can we describe someone who works well with other people?</q>

				<q id='1'>How should you start a letter to someone whose name you don’t know?</q>

				<q id='2'>What four other words can be used instead of ‘job’ in an advertisement?</q>

				<q id='3'>How can we describe a working environment which is busy and rapidly changing?</q>

		</questions>
	</quiz>
</bank>
